<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
	<DoNotAutoCutTrees>DoNotAutoCutTrees</DoNotAutoCutTrees>
	<SettingLabel>Select the groups of pawns, which should be supervised. If any of this pawns get a mood debuff from there ideo by cutting trees, all pawns won't automatically cut trees in growing zones and by building structures and roofing</SettingLabel>
	<SettingIdeoIsColonist>Colonists</SettingIdeoIsColonist>
	<SettingIdeoIsColonistDesc>Do not cut trees if any colonist get a mood debuff from cutting trees</SettingIdeoIsColonistDesc>
	<SettingIdeoIsSlave>Slaves</SettingIdeoIsSlave>
	<SettingIdeoIsSlaveDesc>Do not cut trees if any slave get a mood debuff from cutting trees</SettingIdeoIsSlaveDesc>
	<SettingIdeoIsGuest>Guests</SettingIdeoIsGuest>
	<SettingIdeoIsGuestDesc>Colonist, which joins your colony temporary by a quest</SettingIdeoIsGuestDesc>
	<SettingIdeoIsPrisoner>Prisoners</SettingIdeoIsPrisoner>
	<SettingIdeoIsPrisonerDesc>Do not cut trees if any prisoner get a mood debuff from cutting trees</SettingIdeoIsPrisonerDesc>
	<SettingManualPawnListShort>ManualList</SettingManualPawnListShort>
	<SettingManualPawnList>Manual Pawn List</SettingManualPawnList>
	<SettingManualPawnListDesc>This setting adds a GIZMO button to every pawn with a ideo with a mood debuff by cutting trees. This setting only expands the other settings. For complete manual control deactivate the above settings.(IsColonist, IsSlave, IsGuest and IsPrisoner)</SettingManualPawnListDesc>
	<SettingGeneralShort>General</SettingGeneralShort>
	<SettingGeneral>Always deactivate automatically tree cutting for all pawns</SettingGeneral>
	<SettingGeneralDesc>When this setting is activated all colonist won't automatically cut trees in growing zones, building structures and roofing (no matter their ideo)</SettingGeneralDesc>
	<ShowQuickSettingButton>Show quick setting button</ShowQuickSettingButton>
	<ShowQuickSettingButtonDesc>Adds a button in the right bottom corner. The button opens a float menu to quickly change the settings</ShowQuickSettingButtonDesc>
	<ManualPawnListGizmoLabel>Don't auto cut trees</ManualPawnListGizmoLabel>
	<ManualPawnListGizmoDesc>This setting only expands the other settings. For complete manual control deactivate the other settings.(IsColonist, IsSlave, IsGuest, IsPrisoner)</ManualPawnListGizmoDesc>
	<ManualPawnList>Manual Pawn List</ManualPawnList>
	<ManualPawnListClear>Clear Manual Pawn List</ManualPawnListClear>
</LanguageData>
